{
    "translations": {
        "en": {
            "q2": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "description": "We will construct an algorithm to convert any Right Linear grammar to a Left Linear grammar.",
                "question": "[T|F] finding an algorithm to convert Right Regular Grammar (RRG) to Left Regular Grammar(LRG) means that we proved that any RRG has LRG.",
                "answer": "True",
                "choices": [
                    "True",
                    "False"
                ]
            },
            "q3": {
                "type": "select",
                "description": "During the construction of the algorithm, we will convert the following grammr to Left Linear Grammar.",
                "question": "What is L(G)",
                "answer": [
                    "$a^*cbb^*$",
                    "$\\{a^ncb^m \\mid n\\ge 0, m>0\\}$"
                ],
                "choices": [
                    "$a^*cbb^*$",
                    "$\\{a^ncb^m \\mid n\\ge 0, m>0\\}$"
                ]
            },
            "q4": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "description": "Since the Language $L$ has a Right Linear grammar, we can follow ``NFA from Regular Grammar'' proof in the previous modules to construct an NFA for the language.",
                "question": "What does it mean to follow ``NFA from Regular Grammar'' proof?",
                "answer": "Convert Regular Grammar to NFA",
                "choices": [
                    "Convert NFA to Regular grammar",
                    "Convert Regular Grammar to NFA"
                ]
            },
            "q11": {
                "type": "select",
                "description": "The next step in our algorithm is to REVERSE the NFA.",
                "question": "How can we reverse an NFA?",
                "answer": [
                    "This means that we need to filp all transitions",
                    "Swap the start and final states"
                ],
                "choices": [
                    "This means that we need to filp all transitions",
                    "Swap the start and final states"
                ]
            },
            "q12": {
                "type": "select",
                "description": "Lest us start by reversing the transitions.",
                "question": "What is the result of reversing the transitions $\\delta(S, a) = S$, and $\\delta(A, b) = A$?",
                "answer": [
                    "The edge that represent $\\delta(S, a) = S$ will not change as it is a loop.",
                    "The edge that represent $\\delta(A, b) = A$ will not change as it is a loop."
                ],
                "choices": [
                    "The edge that represent $\\delta(S, a) = S$ will not change as it is a loop.",
                    "The edge that represent $\\delta(A, b) = A$ will not change as it is a loop."
                ]
            },
            "q13": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "description": "Lest us start by reversing the transitions.",
                "question": "What is the result of reversing the transition $\\delta(S, c) = A$?",
                "answer": "$\\delta(A, c) = S$",
                "choices": [
                    "$\\delta(S, a) = S$",
                    "$\\delta(A, b) = A$",
                    "$\\delta(A, c) = S$",
                    "$\\delta(S, c) = A$",
                    "$\\delta(A, b) = F$",
                    "$\\delta(F, b) = A$"
                ]
            },
            "q14": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "description": "Lest us start by reversing the transitions.",
                "question": "What is the result of reversing the transition $\\delta(A, b) = F$?",
                "answer": "$\\delta(F, b) = A$",
                "choices": [
                    "$\\delta(S, a) = S$",
                    "$\\delta(A, b) = A$",
                    "$\\delta(A, c) = S$",
                    "$\\delta(S, c) = A$",
                    "$\\delta(A, b) = F$",
                    "$\\delta(F, b) = A$"
                ]
            },
            "q15": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "description": "All edges are reversed.",
                "question": "What is the next step?",
                "answer": "Swap the start and Final states",
                "choices": [
                    "Done, the NFA is reversed.",
                    "Swap the start and Final states"
                ]
            },
            "q17": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "description": "Convert the final state to be the initital state.",
                "question": "In case that the NFA has multiple final states. How can we convert them to a start state?",
                "answer": "Convert the NFA with multiple final states to an NFA with one final state. Then make the new final state a start state.",
                "choices": [
                    "Convert every final state to a start state",
                    "Convert the NFA with multiple final states to an NFA with one final state. Then make the new final state a start state."
                ]
            },
            "q19": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "description": "We can follow the ``RR Grammar from DFA'' proof from the slides to get the right linear grammar for $NFA_{rev}$. Thus, we have the right linear grammar for $L^R$.",
                "question": "What does it mean to follow ``RR Grammar from DFA'' proof?",
                "answer": "Convert NFA to Regular grammar",
                "choices": [
                    "Convert NFA to Regular grammar",
                    "Convert Regular Grammar to NFA"
                ]
            },
            "q20": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "description": "We can follow the ``RR Grammar from DFA'' proof from the slides to get the right linear grammar for $NFA_{rev}$. Thus, we have the right linear grammar for $L^R$.",
                "question": "What is the production equivelent to the transition $\\delta(S, a) = S$?",
                "answer": "$S\\rightarrow aS$",
                "choices": [
                    "$S\\rightarrow aS$",
                    "$S\\rightarrow Sa$"
                ]
            },
            "q21": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "description": "We can follow the ``RR Grammar from DFA'' proof from the slides to get the right linear grammar for $NFA_{rev}$. Thus, we have the right linear grammar for $L^R$.",
                "question": "What is the production equivelent to the transition $\\delta(A, b) = A$?",
                "answer": "$A\\rightarrow bA$",
                "choices": [
                    "$A\\rightarrow bA$",
                    "$A\\rightarrow Ab$"
                ]
            },
            "q22": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "description": "We can follow the ``RR Grammar from DFA'' proof from the slides to get the right linear grammar for $NFA_{rev}$. Thus, we have the right linear grammar for $L^R$.",
                "question": "What is the production equivelent to the transition $\\delta(A, c) = S$?",
                "answer": "$A\\rightarrow cS$",
                "choices": [
                    "$A\\rightarrow Sc$",
                    "$A\\rightarrow cS$"
                ]
            },
            "q23": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "description": "We can follow the ``RR Grammar from DFA'' proof from the slides to get the right linear grammar for $NFA_{rev}$. Thus, we have the right linear grammar for $L^R$.",
                "question": "What is the production equivelent to the transition $\\delta(F, b) = A$?",
                "answer": "$F\\rightarrow cA$",
                "choices": [
                    "$F\\rightarrow cA$",
                    "$F\\rightarrow Ac$"
                ]
            },
            "q24": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "description": "We can follow the ``RR Grammar from DFA'' proof from the slides to get the right linear grammar for $NFA_{rev}$. Thus, we have the right linear grammar for $L^R$.",
                "question": "What is the resulting Grammar Language?",
                "answer": "The resulting Grammar is the Right Linear Grammar for the reverse of the original Language",
                "choices": [
                    "The resulting Grammar is the Right Linear Grammar for the original Language",
                    "The resulting Grammar is the Right Linear Grammar for the reverse of the original Language"
                ]
            },
            "q26": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "description": "By reversing each production in the resulting Right Linear grammar, we will get the the Left Linear grammar for the reverse of $L^R$. So, we have the Left Linear grammar for $(L^R)^R = L$.",
                "question": "What is the result of reversing $S\\rightarrow aS$?",
                "answer": "$S\\rightarrow Sa$",
                "choices": [
                    "$S\\rightarrow aS$",
                    "$S\\rightarrow Sa$"
                ]
            },
            "q27": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "description": "By reversing each production in the resulting Right Linear grammar, we will get the the Left Linear grammar for the reverse of $L^R$. So, we have the Left Linear grammar for $(L^R)^R = L$.",
                "question": "What is the result of reversing $A\\rightarrow bA$?",
                "answer": "$A\\rightarrow Ab$",
                "choices": [
                    "$A\\rightarrow bA$",
                    "$A\\rightarrow Ab$"
                ]
            },
            "q28": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "description": "By reversing each production in the resulting Right Linear grammar, we will get the the Left Linear grammar for the reverse of $L^R$. So, we have the Left Linear grammar for $(L^R)^R = L$.",
                "question": "What is the result of reversing $A\\rightarrow cS$?",
                "answer": "$A\\rightarrow cS$",
                "choices": [
                    "$A\\rightarrow Sc$",
                    "$A\\rightarrow cS$"
                ]
            },
            "q29": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "description": "By reversing each production in the resulting Right Linear grammar, we will get the the Left Linear grammar for the reverse of $L^R$. So, we have the Left Linear grammar for $(L^R)^R = L$.",
                "question": "What is the result of reversing $F\\rightarrow bA$?",
                "answer": "$F\\rightarrow Ab$",
                "choices": [
                    "$F\\rightarrow bA$",
                    "$F\\rightarrow Ab$"
                ]
            },
            "q30": {
                "type": "multiple",
                "description": "Done. We reversed all productions",
                "question": "What is the type of the resulting grammar?",
                "answer": "Left Regular Grammar",
                "choices": [
                    "Right Regular Grammar",
                    "Left Regular Grammar",
                    "Linear Grammar"
                ]
            }
        }
    }
}